So next, we're going to add some lip color to Sherry.
So, rather than using a full lipstick, especially for Spring makeup, I don't really think that you need it so I'm actually going to use a stain on Sherry.
So I'm just going to use my ring finger and I'm just going to start to kind of dab this, right on her lip and you can see it automatically gives color, but because it's a stain, it's going to stay all day.
And this is more of like, this kind of Hot Pink-Red and it sort of gives that Bee Stung look.
It's really, really pretty and you can see how pretty it is with that purple that we have on her lids.
So, I'm just going to blend this in really lightly.
I'm not going to do a ton, 'cause she really doesn't need it.
You definitely can use a lip brush if you want to but you don't have to.
You can also use a lip liner if you feel like you need a little bit more definition, I definitely understand that.
Sherry doesn't necessarily need it, so we're going to skip the liner with this today but, and using a brush to put on this stain is going to give you a lot more color, but I just sort of want to give the Bee Sting look, so I'm just going to pat it right on her lip and leave it at that.